Red.
Holy shit, have you seen the virtual campus?
Today the Culture class is in classroom 110.
Well, let's go over there, otherwise there won't be any room...
No, we had breakfast, we relaxed and already...
Well, I was already in the mood to sit down with my fellows, who'd stick their hands in my back.
Aren't you angry?
The exercise is good.
In addition, the Ball is the bomb as a teacher.
But let's see, explain it to me.
I mean, did she tell you I'd be late for class?
No, no. He told us that if someone was late, he would ask us the color of the folder and that we would say red.
It's just that if you think about it, it's good.
But he's got a cruel little dot.
You won't say it for me.
I'm going there, and then there won't be room and there won't be...
Save for everyone.
But there's class at 110?
How do you like to play, huh?
To the ball more.
And now, repeat all with me.
Once again.
You know, I don't think you're that calm.
After the "momentazo" that made you pass the Ball...
- No, man, but first it doesn't fix your job, now this...
What's wrong with you?
But you followed the game, that pisses me off.
You could have told me he was going to play with me.
First you go as a friend, but then, take it!
Don't be mad, we'll have a beer tonight and we'll disconnect.
Okay.
- On the floor of Minerva.
I just talked to her, she's got a beautiful terrace.
I'll tell you, I'm keeping track of working hours.
Dude, what are you doing in a fucking parking lot?
Do as Minerva, quit the job.
Hi, Rai.
What's up?
How's it going, Schopenhauer?
We haven't gotten to him yet.
I also know a little bit of philosophy.
I think so.
Your mother's in the garden.
Distracted, reading...
Where the hell is Saint Peter of Verona?
Mom!
Is it true you stole my painting?
You're talking about robbery?
Did you steal it from the grandparents by taking advantage of the fact that they were at Calella's house?
I saved the painting.
Your husband would've taken out four tough ones.
Are you trying to justify you breaking into grandparents' house?
Let's calm down a little? -An Italian expert in Baroque painting will go to the auction house in Madrid.
Julia wants me to certify if the painting can be attributed to Claudio Coello. I don't know if you know who it is.
Look, two little things.
First, Julia get fucked, yeah, fuck Julia.
And second, you send the Italian a picture and shit.
Is this the philosophy of your new career?
- Will you shut up, please?
Victoria, it's attributable to Coello. I told you, it looks a lot like the Santo Domingo Museum in Budapest.
Maybe the Italian won't be necessary.
Now all of a sudden you're interested in painting?
If you don't even come near the auction house.
Look, let the painting stay.
And tomorrow you come to the inauguration of the new exhibition.
So you show a little interest in mom's work.
And I don't like you talking to him like that.
You're going, huh, Rai?
I'm going.
Until tomorrow. -Bye.
No, Gloria, I don't understand classical music and stuff.
- I'm tired of arguing.
It's okay.
Enjoy the concert.
Gloria, you look beautiful.
Thank you, at least you tell me.
What's the first thing I told you?
Your father doesn't want to accompany me to a piano concert.
See if you calm him down, I can't and I'll be late.
I'm leaving, too.
Look who I've met.
All right.
Well, what a pimp this is, isn't it?
It's a fucking guy.
Funny, French, pianist...
Well, he's got everything, isn't he?
And Rai with whom does he speak?
You have to meet her.
It's a "person."
- Hey.
Amy O'Connor, I'm from Eugene, Origin.
Watch out he's got a gun under his pillow.
- Okay, listen.
No, of course.
- I said...
Like a tradition.
A tradition, like Halloween, right?
- I know it's not the same, you don't understand because you don't listen.
Pol, listen.
No, wait a minute, wait a minute.
Not bad, no, the question. Think a little.
You call the police and wait?
I'm sorry about your family, but they're all dead.
My father has a hunting shotgun...
I mean, if he comes in and steals from you, they wouldn't steal anything from me.
Does family deserve you to kill for them?
Okay, guys, that's enough. I've got the final debate.
- Do we have the ass we deserve?
I do.
Play, play.
- I love it.
Don't I have a good ass?
It's nice, isn't it?
- Bye.
Fuck, Pol, are you yawning already, man?
That's why you'd better not come, stay home.
The butler is waiting for you at the door, or what?
I came by myself.
Did you get the subway?
Don't get too attached, man.
Be happy, put your money on a chauffeur.
You're one of those who think money is happiness, aren't you?
I don't know.
What do you think?
I think...
I'm the only philosophy student who doesn't care if the career has a way out.
Go on, go on.
Well, it's very simple.
There are things in my life that don't work, but...
I'm so relaxed!
No, there's more, there's still more.
When we're 40 years old, you'll look... 50 and me, 35.
What bulbs? The green ones or the red ones?
Can you help me, Pol, I don't know right now, I don't...
Who were you a year ago?
Who were you?
Who were you with?
Didn't you have any posh friends?
Yeah, yeah, I'm expired.
What are you doing? Are you looking for friends among the poor?
Why do you get so low? Isn't that what you need us for?
Impossible, isn't it?
You could be home, without stress, slowly aging and surrounded by the family.
Hey, Pol, don't fuck off!
- No, no, stay.
Stay, I stole a beer from the American.
See if there's any luck and we don't get shot.
Long live Mississippi!
You, today in class, when the Ball has done the folder exercise, I wanted to hug you.
Look, that's it.
Okay, okay.
Oti... go.
Okay. All right, all right, please!
I like you very much, but I don't want anything with you, okay?
I just think Amy's beer goes up a lot.
It's okay.
You can go upstairs and give you some air.
No, no, I'd better go home.
- It's not uncommon for us to throw the shingles at you.
I don't understand French.
I understand.
The Catalans are very discreet.
How's the party?
Good.
Oh, he called Oriol.
Don't call him Oriol, who's my father.
I'd like to know if we'll be up on Sunday.
They're setting up a barbecue.
No, I don't want to go.
It's just that my father gives me a stick with his monologues on football.
You've had a drink, haven't you?
A little bit.
Well, I'd love to go up to town.
Let's see people.
Fuck, what "heavy"!
I'm staying here.
It's just that I've discovered...
I'm cosmopolitan.
It's confirmed: you've been drinking.
Come on, let's go to sleep. "No, you sleep here, I want to sleep wide in bed.
And so I put myself on a cross, and undo it when I feel like it.
And you're going to leave me alone?
It makes me so bad that you have some gray hair...
Oh, yeah?
Sorry, you can't sit here.
Looks like an 80-year-old lady died who came as a listener and didn't...
Don't you want to know what he did a year ago?
A year ago, I realized that my father cheated on my grandfather to steal his company.
And I was very touched, because I realized that I look like my father.
And yes, I recognize that sometimes...
I can give you a little rage.
More like a lot of rage.
A lot.
One to zero.
One to zero from what?
Well, I've explained one thing to you...
staff that, for me, is not pleasant.
And you?
Do you have any weak points you want to explain to me?
According to Aristóteles, who had to have the best flutes were the best flute players.
It was a way to reward them for their musical virtue.
In politics it would also have to be so, that the most exemplary citizens were those who agreed to the political charges of the most responsibility.
Plato and Aristótela had it very clear: politics has to be decent because an indecent destroys everything that rules.
And you, if in the future you were dedicated to politics, would you be intelligent?
We all know we don't have to steal.
Fuck, what an exemplary class.
If the boss pays me an extra in black money, I love it.
What's wrong?
Let's see, Silvia, the first day of class you told us that the associate teachers will charge, at most, 500 euros.
I see you want to cheer me up today.
Okay, excuse me. Also, university fees are scandalously high and to the many who ask for a scholarship, or we approve everything or they throw us out.
Faced with this panorama, who of you would reject an envelope with money? Come on, raise your hand.
It is clear that the Treasury should not be let down and that moral principles should be those, but the problem is that people move away from the system because it is very punishing.
Could you explain it a little more?
Well, I don't know, my father a few years ago...
I'm serious, listen to me.
And he, for being punctual and working well, was paid a bonus.
So why does the system not reward exemplary citizens?
Paying taxes is your obligation.
Okay, but I insist, there are millions of people paying their taxes all their lives and in the end, what do they receive when they retire?
-Pol, you're an anti-system.
Marqués de Casamiquela, I love the system.
The problem is that the system doesn't want me.
Wait a minute, wait a minute.
Pol, the system has to monitor and punish the corrupt, otherwise everything goes to hell.
Let's see, Biel, a little thing, who cares about a parent who only punishes?
We also like to be pampered a little, don't we?
And why are our good deeds not rewarded?
I wonder: wouldn't the fraudsters diminish if they rewarded us when we behaved well?
Wouldn't there be less corrupt?
It's a question I leave in the air.
Honestly, if I spend my life paying my taxes religiously, I'd like to receive a letter from the IRS saying...
No, nothing, nothing.
You want me to come with you?
That's good.
What are you doing?
Hangover?
Listen, yesterday was already... it was bad.
But, well, I won't fool you, I know what I'm doing.
It's okay, Oti.
- Sure, I like you very much.
In addition, we all have our desires.
I want us to be friends.
In the end what?
Do we have the ass we deserve or not?
Hey, we're here to pay for the card.
Oh, girl, is that, on Mandri Street, what did you expect?
Go to Ronda Mitre, by the way.
- Not so much laugh, Ester, I'm not stupid.
Susana, don't be angry.
How about the exhibition? Are you going to buy something?
Oh, buy a painting, your walls are so boring.
Sure, buy pictures, instead of stealing them.
Don't start, do me a favor.
If you come to say nonsense, you better get out.
Mom, I told you he'd come.
Fuck, Ester, what about this coat?
Do you like it?
Minerva Picotti, my mother, my aunt Ester and her friends.
What was your name again?
Rai, how ugly!
That's nice!
Esther, please!
Well, we're over here.
In Argentina they're terrible, aren't they?
- Shut up, he'll hear you.
My mother doesn't know me.
When I was little, I never gave myself what I wanted.
If I asked for a toy car, she sent someone to buy me a big motor car, you know?
Sometimes I miss reading a book.
In the "insti" I read "The story of a castaway".
It's short, but it's okay, huh?
Today, in class, the Weierstrass theorem was explained to us.
Here?
According to the theorem, if a function ephe...
Of equis...
It's continuous in an interval...
a, b, then, efe...
It's narrowed down in this interval.
"Filled down" means that it is limited by two numbers: above...
And down there.
That I don't want to be sold, I want it for myself.
What's wrong with you?
Okay, no, Minerva, I didn't mean that.
I've been offered a job in a high school.
The next course.
He'd charge twice as much.
I'm not so clear.
I don't know, the truth is I feel good here, I feel motivated.
And more now, that first-timers are better than last year's.
And so much! Today in class a superchulo debate has been organized, they have not stopped intervening.
I'm not kidding.
I have a feeling they like me.
That's why I hesitate to leave.
Here I have students...
especially interesting.
It's cool in the fall, isn't it?
It's dark before.
Okay. Was that it?
Shall we take a break? I have a croissant.
If you give me half.
Leave it.
No, well, yeah, I'll let you bite it.
You're funny enough, man, huh?
Why? I look smaller, don't I?
Have you fallen in love or what?
Hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey!
You can't fall in love so fast.
I'm in love with Minerva.
But she prefers art rather than croissants.
Did you say something?
How's it going?
You were right.
What the ball did to me the other day in class didn't bother me at all.
I felt humiliated.
I recognize that...
I don't like to lose.
And what pisses me off is that I'm known to be lost.
Please rate this subtitle at www.osdb.link/6y8jb Help others choose the best